Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers, 1881-1978, and undated
Finley, Nellie May Davis.
25 cubic feet (in 25 boxes, 1 Oversized folder)
MSS.
Papers of Nellie Finley, as a student and a teacher, and her family of Parma, Michigan.
Clarke Historical Library, Central Michigan University
Acc# 72943
Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers are open for research.
Biography:
Nellie Mae, or May, Davis Finley (1888-1940s), was born in Michigan, the daughter of Wilson H. and Martha J. Finley. Wilson was a farmer born in 1848 in New York State, the home state of his parents. Martha was born in Michigan in 1852, but her parents were from Pennsylvania. In 1907 Nellie graduated from Michigan State Normal School. In July 1912 Nellie married Theron S. Finley (1887-died before 1920), the son of Erwin J. Finley, a farmer in Parma, Jackson County, Michigan. In 1914-1915 Theron suffered from tuberculosis and was hospitalized. Theron died in early 1920. That year, Nellie Finley lived with her parents and her mother’s sister, Nellie McEntire, and Nellie’s two sons, Theron W., age six, and Harry C., age four, in Parma. The 1930 Federal Census for Michigan records that they were still all living together in Parma, except for Nellie McEntire who had probably died. In both the 1920 and 1930 Federal Censuses for Michigan Nellie is listed as a public school teacher. In the 1920 census Nellie was listed as a widow with her maiden name of Davis. She taught at Devereaux School (Jackson County, Michigan), 1926-1927. Nellie was still alive in the 1940s. (This information is from the collection and AncestryLibrary.com viewed in June 2011.)
From the collection we know the Nellie apparently collected historical information. In 1937 she was approached by the University of Michigan Archives to donate collections she might have of state historical value. There are several letters between her, Harry Brown, and L. G. Vandevelde concerning collections in 1937 and 1939. Also from the collection we know the Harry C. Finley was honorably discharged from the War Department in 1937 and was a Professor of Military Science and Tactics at Michigan Technological University in Houghton, Michigan.
An image of Orlando H. Moore, described on a note in the collection as Orlando de Moore, is included in the oversized materials. Moore enlisted at Schoolcraft as a Second Lieutenant in the Sixth U.S. Infantry on June 27, 1856. He was promoted to First Lieutenant on March 2, 1861, to Captain on May 26, 1861, and as Lieutenant Colonel of the Thirteenth Michigan Infantry when it was organized on December 28, 1861. The unit mustered on January 16, 1862. Moore was commissioned Colonel of the Twenty-fifth Infantry when it was organized on August 18, 1862. After commanding a brigade, he was mustered out on June 24, 1865. Moore was promoted to Major, Sixth U.S. Infantry on June 8, 1874, and Lieutenant Colonel, Seventeenth U.S. Infantry on April 11, 1882. For gallant and meritorious service in action at Tebb’s Bend, Kentucky Moore was prompted first to the rank of Brevet Major, on July 4, 1863, and was later to Lieutenant Colonel on March 13, 1865. Moore retired from the army on April 15, 1884 and died at Dearborn, Michigan, on October 31, 1890. (This information is from the regimental history of the 25th Michigan Infantry.)
Boxes 1-24 are roughly foldered probably in original order which is somewhat alphabetical and somewhat chronological. Staff at the time, before 1997, simply put one letter in a folder and labeled it to X from Y with a date. There was no processing at that time. Box 25 was actually processed by the Archivist and is organized both alphabetically and chronologically.
Family Papers, 1881-1978, and undated, measures 25 cubic ft. (in 25 boxes, 1 Oversized folder). It consists of the papers of Nellie Finley and her family, including correspondence, teaching materials she used as a student and a teacher, notebooks, scrapbooks, published materials, photographs, and miscellaneous. The correspondence, in Boxes 1-21 and 25, includes letters, notes, telegrams, greeting cards, and postcards, and may include newspaper clippings and/or photographs, mostly exchanged between Nellie and her friends and relatives, 1881-1934, and undated. It is not always possible to determine the relationships between the correspondents, but this has been noted, when possible. The collection is mostly organized in alphabetical and chronological order with published and miscellaneous items after correspondence. There are also receipts, speeches, miscellaneous materials, certificates, recitation and student notebooks, and a few miscellaneous scrapbooks and recipes. Box 21 consists entirely of greeting cards organized by holiday or occassion. Published items in Boxes 22-24 include pages of partial directories of Michigan teachers, 1886-1903, and a directory of superintendents and principals, 1890-1891. Of note among the published volumes are Michigan poet Will Carleton's Everywhere, January-December 1911, Christoforo’s Method for Mandolin (Music Instruction Book, Copyright 1897 - John Church Co.), and the 77th Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction of the State of Michigan w/ Accompanying Documents for the Year 1913-1914.
Note: The abbreviations ND stands for Nellie May Davis and NDF for Nellie D. Finley.
Box 25 (Acc# 72943) includes family correspondence, some of Nellie’s early school materials she created as a child, and materials documenting Masonic organizations such as the Order of the Eastern Star, Michigan State Normal School, and Michigan insurance companies.
The Oversized folder includes Nellie and Theron’s marriage certificate, 1912, and Nellie’s Parma High School diploma, 1904. Also included is an oversized, undated, post-Civil gravure print of Orlando H. Moore holding a bugle and wearing a cape in civilian clothes. He does not appear to be related to the Finleys.
Processing Note: Prior to 1997, students and perhaps Clarke staff simply foldered this collection and likely maintained its loose original order. The original finding aid is no longer accessible on the computer due to software changes. Due to other priorities it was decided not to re-process the collection or individually cataloged published materials. Box 25 was a late addition in 2011 which was processed by the Archivist. A formal finding aid with biographical section and scope notes were not created until 2011 by Archivist Marian Matyn.
Processing Note: Eight oversized Masonic certificates of Edgar A. Guest were donated with Acc# 72943. These were added to the existing Guest papers.
Subjects:
Finley, Nellie May Davis.; Moore, Orlando Hurley, 1827-1890.; Carleton, Will, 1845-1912.; Finley family.; Michigan State University--Alumni and alumnae.; Parma High School (Parma, Mich.); Devereaux School (Jackson County, Mich.); United States.--Army.--Michigan Infantry Regiment 25th (1862-1865)--History.; Order of the Eastern Star.; Tuberculosis hospitals--Michigan--Wayne County--History.; Teachers--Michigan--Parma.; Teachers--Michigan--Jackson County.; Mandolin music.; Scrapbooks--Michigan.; Education--Directories--Michigan.; Freemasonry--Michigan.; United States--History--Civil War, 1861-1865.
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Alice,December 28, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. All,November 29, 30, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Amy,December 19, [no year] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to: Will From: M. G. Andrews,August 25, [no year] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: Will From: M. G. Andrews,October 31, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: Will From: M. G. Andrews,October 11, 191- (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: M. G. Andrews,April 21 [no year] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: M. G. Andrews,July 19, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Emma Bower,November 1, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. McMurtrie From: Mrs. E. E. Burchard,November 28, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Clarence,May 6, [no year] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis and family From: Anna Corbett,December 27, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. John Crawford,February 5, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: the Davises From: E. D. Darling,September 21, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: the Davises From: E. D. Darling,August 10, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: the Davises From: E. D. Darling,October 14, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis and Children From: W. H. Davis,July 8, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis and Children From: W. H. Davis,July 15, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis and Children From: W. H. Davis,July 29, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis and Children From: W. H. Davis,July 21, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis and Children From: W. H. Davis,April 9, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis and Children From: W. H. Davis,July 31, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Mrs. W. H. Davis (Mattie),August 7, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: Friend From: the Dopp Family,November 3, [no year] (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: Friend From: the Dopp Family,undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: Harry Davis From: the Dopp Family,June 6, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. H. K. Farrand, Mrs. C. H. F., and Maggie,April 12, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Gertie Gilleo,August 4, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Susie M. H.,August 17, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis and Nellie From: Anna,February 21, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: Cousin Harry From: Artie McMurtrie,March 28, 1886? (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Parents (Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis) From: Harry (and Zoe) Davis,1886-1900 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Parents (Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis) From: Harry (and Zoe) Davis,1904-1909 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Pamela Hill,October 10, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Pamela Hill,May 12, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Pamela Hill,February 23, [no year] (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Pamela Hill,December 31, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Pamela Hill,May 30, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Rebecca Herrick,April 30, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Rebecca Herrick,February 23, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Rebecca Herrick,June 16, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: Aunt Mattie (Mrs. W. H.) Davis From: Jessie,February 13, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: Aunt Mattie (Mrs. W. H.) Davis From: Jessie,January 8, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. Lambirs?,December 12, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Viola Lawrence,June 12, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Viola Lawrence,March 27, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Philena and Anna Leidy,1891-1903 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Addie McMurtrie,1885-1891 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Jessica McMurtrie,1882-1897 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis and Nellie From: Nellie McMurtrie,1886-1907 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. Bart Miller,May 26, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. Bart Miller,June 7, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Lida Miller,September 30, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Lida Miller,June 18, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mother,1886-1896 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Minnie S. Osmun,June 6, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Minnie S. Osmun,July 14, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. H. Pitts,July 18, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Belle Ranch,September 20, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Belle Ranch,February 7, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Belle Ranch,January 6, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Belle Ranch,May 3, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Marianne Scurrah,1891-1898 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Francis Stamp,August 18, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Francis Stamp,March 21, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Francis Stamp,March 21, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Jane H. Swan,1885-1894 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Unknown,April 29, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harriet Weston,September 26, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: J. L. W.,December 27, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: J. L. W.,October 24, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Ruth Westover,April 25, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Ruth Westover,September 3, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Eva Wolford,1881-1897 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence to: Cousin Harry From: Anna E. Leidy,July 18, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to: Anna and Gertie From: Lizzie,August 26, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to: Anna and Gertie From: Lizzie,June 7, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to: Rachel From: the Moore Family,February 22, 1860 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence to: Martha Slack From: the Moore Family,August 26, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. George Hoag From: May Wertnizton,June 25, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis, From: Land Contract and Payment Receipts,January 7, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis, From: The Epwork League Social Invitation,January 3, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: Harry E. Davis From: Unknown,July 8, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Laura E. and Chummy Titus,1907-1909 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Laura E. and Chummy Titus,1907-1909 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence (many) to: Cousin From: A. T. Tweedie,March-August 1910 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Earle Tweedie,November 13, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Earle Tweedie,June 21, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Earle Tweedie,November 28, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Jessie Tweedie,March 21, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Unknown,October 4, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Unknown,October 7, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Unknown,December 23, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Herbert Tweedie,1900-1910 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Vesta,1907-1909 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Blanche Wilder,1890-1900 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Cleve Wolcott,1905-1908 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: businesses,1905-1909 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: County Commissioner of Schools,1904-1906 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Teaching Jobs,1908-1910 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Invitations,1898-1909 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: ND, From: Poem "Too Bad",1905? (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Order of the Eastern Star,November 17, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Order of the Eastern Star,December 7, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND, From: School Records,1901-1907? (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. Earle M. Horton From: Nellie M. Davis (ND),May 24, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Anna,August 21, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Aunt ?,November 12, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Aunt ?,December 15, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Aunt ?,July 14, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Aunt ?,June 6, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Amy Bacon,May 6, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Amy Bacon,December 6, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Amy Bacon,February 10, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Amy Bacon,October 13, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Amy Bacon,April 9, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (many) to: ND From: Bessie,undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Erma Bloom,December 17, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: R. D. Brewer,February 28, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: R. D. Brewer,August 21, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: ND (Tige?) From: Buster,September 18, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: ND (Tige?) From: Buster,July 15, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: ND (Tige?) From: Buster,April 24, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: ND (Tige?) From: Buster,September 26, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,July 16, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,June 15, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,May 15, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,April 11, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,March 13, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,March 20, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,February 13, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,November 27, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hugh C.,November 8, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Nettie Campbell,June 15, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Grace Carson,April 22, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Grace Carson,April 25, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Grace Carson,July 20, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Grace Carson,November 5, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: May L. Carson,July 26, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: May L. Carson,January 29, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: May L. Carson (folder 1 of 2),May 12, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: May L. Carson (folder 2 of 2),May 12, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: May L. Carson,May 26, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,July 5, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,October 20, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,July 19, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,May 8, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,April 14, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,March 7, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,December 9, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,September 30, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,April 9, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,February 3, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Helen Chapel,December 2, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Anna Corbett,October 9, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Anna Corbett,August 31, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Anna Corbett,October 31, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Anna Corbett,December 6, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Anna Corbett,October 7, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,January 13, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,January 24, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,March 24, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 25, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 20, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 14, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 15, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 3, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 28, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,November 14, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,January 9, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 24, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,May 8, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 12, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,July 31, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 3, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 1, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry and Zoe Davis,October 9, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Weston and Loretta Davis,February 6, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Weston and Loretta Davis,April 3, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Weston and Loretta Davis,May 29, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Weston and Loretta Davis,July 17, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Weston and Loretta Davis,December 21, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Weston and Loretta Davis,November 6, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Weston and Loretta Davis,October 3, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis (Parents),October 26, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis (Parents),October 8, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis (Parents),October 19, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 81)